=Deity of Love= =Episode 15=
= إله الحب = = الحلقة 15 =
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
I'm not leaving.
لن أغادر.
I'll get you some soup.
سأحضر لك بعض الحساء.
I know she is not reliable.
أعلم أنها غير موثوقة.
How could she leave Brother Xiuning here?
كيف يمكنها ترك الأخ Xiuning هنا؟
Brother Xiuning, let go of me. What are you doing?
الأخ Xiuning ، اترك لي.  ماذا تفعل؟
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
It's all your fault.
هذا كله خطأك.
It's you who make Brother Xiuning do that to me.
أنت الذي جعل الأخ Xiuning يفعل ذلك بي.
Such a grudge
يا له من ضغينة
is a great food.
هو طعام رائع.
Demon, you...
شيطان ، أنت ...
Do you know where it is?
هل تعرف أين هو؟
You dare to come here casually.
أنت تجرؤ على المجيء إلى هنا بشكل عرضي.
How could I not know this place?
كيف لا اعرف هذا المكان؟
And I know more about
وأنا أعرف المزيد عن
what you are thinking.
بما تفكر.
What I am thinking
ما أفكر فيه
is none of your business.
ليس من شأنك.
I can help you
أستطيع مساعدتك
get the man you want.
احصل على الرجل الذي تريده.
(I can get close to Li Xiuning with this body.)
(يمكنني الاقتراب من Li Xiuning بهذه الجسد.)
Brother Xiuning must belong to me.
يجب أن ينتمي الأخ Xiuning لي.
No one can take him away.
لا أحد يستطيع أن يأخذه بعيدا.
(Just let him drink this.)
(فقط دعه يشرب هذا).
(I promise you both will satisfy your desires)
(أعدك أن كلاكما سوف يرضي رغباتك)
(and he will never leave you.)
(ولن يتركك أبدًا.)
(What are you doing?)
(ماذا تفعل؟)
(It's the wrong direction.)
(إنه الاتجاه الخاطئ).
I'll kill her.
سوف اقتلها.
As long as I kill her,
ما دمت أقتلها ،
Brother Xiuning is mine.
الأخ Xiuning هو لي.
(It's more important to find Li Xiuning.)
(من المهم جدًا العثور على Li Xiuning.)
It's you.
انه انت.
You bad woman,
أنت امرأة سيئة
go to hell.
اذهب إلى الجحيم.
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
To kill you, of course.
لقتلك بالطبع.
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك.
And Brother Xiuning will be mine.
وسيكون الأخ Xiuning لي.
Li Xiuning.
لي شيونينغ.
It's Li Xiuning again.
إنه لي Xiuning مرة أخرى.
Why can't I beat her?
لماذا لا أستطيع أن أضربها؟
(Because you're stupid.)
(لأنك غبي.)
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Ning Yu.
نينغ يو.
You stop!
توقف أنت!
What else can you do? Help me!
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل أيضا؟  ساعدني!
(Demonic energy?)
(طاقة شيطانية؟)
(I'll be found if we keep fighting.)
(سأعثر عليها إذا واصلنا القتال).
Demon?
شيطان؟
You...
أنت...
You haven't finished what you promised me.
أنت لم تكمل ما وعدتني به.
At least let me replenish my energy.
على الأقل اسمحوا لي أن أجدد طاقتي.
You can be together forever
يمكنك أن تكون معا إلى الأبد
after I kill your Brother Xiuning.
بعد أن قتلت أخيك Xiuning.
Freeze!
تجمد!
Don't be nervous.
لا تكن عصبيا.
We are both demons.
كلانا شياطين.
There's no need being wary of me.
لا داعي للحذر مني.
I
أنا
am a demon.
أنا شيطان.
You are the same as me.
أنت مثلي.
Piss off.
اغرب عن وجهي.
Even if I am a demon,
حتى لو كنت شيطانًا ،
we are different.
نحن مختلفون.
Some demon showed up in Qingyun Valley.
ظهر بعض الشياطين في وادي تشينغيون.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
You'll die if you stay here.
ستموت إذا بقيت هنا.
Why don't you leave with me?
لماذا لا ترحل معي
They won't.
لن يفعلوا.
You're a demon.
أنت شيطان.
It's right that demons stay with demons.
من الصواب أن تبقى الشياطين مع الشياطين.
Nonsense!
كلام فارغ!
Go!
يذهب!
Go away!
يبتعد!
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
(Someone's coming.)
(شخص ما قادم.)
(You explain to them.)
(أنت تشرح لهم.)
You vicious demon,
أنت شيطان شرير ،
how dare you kill people in Qingyun Valley?
كيف تجرؤ على قتل الناس في وادي تشينغيون؟
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
I didn't kill anyone.
أنا لم أقتل أحدا.
We saw it with our own eyes.
رأينا ذلك بأعيننا.
It can't be more convincing.
لا يمكن أن يكون أكثر إقناعا.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(حق إعادة بث المسرحية على الإنترنت ملك لي.) (شركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co.، Ltd.)